# Ben Hur



bhur777@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/benhur93



https://bhur.dev/

# Summary

I am a Front-End Web Developer with experience in building websites and web applications.

Currently, I am building projects with React, JavaScript, and have experience working with other technologies such as Next.js, Express, Node, Python, Django/Flask and SQL.

#Visit my website: bhur.dev

Check out my GitHub Profile: github.com/BenHur28

# **Experience**



#### Web Developer

Currently Seeking New Opportunities

May 2022 - Present (1 year 4 months)

Able to design and implement frontend interfaces and backend services to assemble web applications based on popular web applications.

Built and tested REST APIs using model driven development and modern frameworks.

Built responsive, accessible, and dynamic web pages to enable users to easily navigate the site.

## TECHNICAL Support Engineer

#### **TIBCO**

May 2020 - May 2022 (2 years 1 month)

Tested and debugged software product issues to create/report JIRA tickets.

Collaborated with internal Product Managers to help improve the product.

Assist in training new employees on company protocols and best practices for approaching technical

Regularly selected to field escalations and live calls providing immediate resolution in product down situations.

# ப்த் Support Specialist

ibi | Information Builders

May 2019 - May 2021 (2 years 1 month)

Worked with WebFocus, a proprietary software platform that allows users to create, analyze, and collaborate on analytics content for business purposes.

Worked in a team environment to help deliver technical support to clients for company software.

## **Education**



#### Queens College

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science 2015 - 2018

# Skills

TypeScript • JavaScript • Next.js • React.js • Node.js • MongoDB • Python (Programming Language) • Django • Flask • Tailwind CSS